websiteforever.com 2011-09-03

# Safest Website Builder for Students

This Privacy Statement governs the manner in which WebsiteForever ("WebsiteForever" or "we") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from customers in connection with WebsiteForever web services including web hosting, secure certificates, E-Commerce Solutions, and other internet services. WebsiteForever reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement and its policies prospectively at any time, subject to applicable laws and regulations, by posting notice of such changes on its web sites.

Privacy:  
WebsiteForever is committed to safeguarding the information its customers entrust to it. WebsiteForever believes in the Safe Harbor principles published by the U.S. Department of Commerce. <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/sh_documents.html>

The Personal Information We Collect:  
WebsiteForever may collect personally identifiable information from customers in a variety of ways, including online and offline subscription and order forms, paper or telephone submissions, and other instances where customers are invited to volunteer such information. Additionally, contact information may be collected during any correspondence relating to customer support, as well as in connection with products and services offered on WebsiteForever sites. We may collect your name, business name and type, address, phone number, email address, domain details, websites url, billing information including credit card number and expiration date. We only use your name, address, billing information/credit card information to process your order. The addresses are used for customer support, required notifications, product and policy updates and marketing releases. Under no circumstances will we use this information for anything else not described in this privacy notice. All users may at any time opt-out of our marketing by clicking the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of all marketing and membership notices.

Financial Information:  
Whenever customers apply for services or sign up for any other product or service through WebsiteForever, we may require financial information such as a credit card number and billing address before we will process that application. We will not sell, share or rent any financial information collected except as disclosed in this policy or as necessary to fulfill orders. 

Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses:  
IP addresses are collected from all visitors to the WebsiteForever Site. IP addresses are used to administer the daily operations of our site, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to help prevent fraud.

Data Integrity:  
We make diligent efforts to maintain accurate information on our customers. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, WebsiteForever has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

Data Security:  
WebsiteForever has put stringent security procedures in place to protect information collected about our customers. We constantly monitor our systems, which are protected using industry-standard security measures. Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") connections are used to communicate to our system to protect Customer financial information as well as encrypting vital information that customers input through WebsiteForever's web sites. However, WebsiteForever cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

Data Access:  
Customers may access all personal identifiable information that we collect and maintain by contacting customer support 24/7. They can correct factual errors in personally identifiable information by sending us a request to our support department, [helpdesk@WebsiteForever.com](mailto:helpdesk@websiteforever.com). To protect Customer privacy and security, WebsiteForever reserves the right to take reasonable steps to verify Customer identity prior to granting access or processing changes or corrections. 

Cookies:  
WebsiteForever uses "cookie" technology in order to enhance our Clients' online experience and for authentication purposes, associating them with your personally identifiable information. They are also used for measuring certain traffic patterns, and to preclude you from having to re-enter your password during multiple visits to the site. Additionally, cookies can track your progress in online promotions so you receive coupons that may be available to you. Cookies may also be used by advertising service vendors that place ads on our site and to authenticate access to additional services provided by WebsiteForever at other web sites. Web browsers may be set to disable cookies, but please note that certain WebsiteForever services may not function correctly if cookies are not enabled.

How Information is Used:  
WebsiteForever may contact customers regarding products and services offered by WebsiteForever and its trusted affiliates, business partners, and independent contractors. We may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and related marketing, advertising and sales efforts. Information will only be made publicly available where mandated by governing agencies or as disclosed in the terms and conditions of our agreements with customers. We will not post any testimonials or comments made by our clients without their explicit permission. 

Electronic Mail:  
Electronic communications may be sent by WebsiteForever using customers' personal contact information to inform them of important industry news or about general services and upgrades provided by WebsiteForever. If customers do not wish to receive these industry notices, they can contact their account manager. However, in order to fulfill our service obligations, WebsiteForever will continue to send emails regarding Customers' account administration or service interruptions for system maintenance. 

Disclosure:  
Information collected from customers may be disclosed to independent contractors and business partners who have agreed to hold this information in confidence, not use it for any purpose except to carry out the service they are providing for WebsiteForever, and honor our privacy and security policies in the way this information is handled. WebsiteForever may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from customers to actual or prospective investors and partners. Should a sale of WebsiteForever's business ever occur, collected Customer information may be transferred along with the sale but the information will be treated in the same manner as this privacy policy.

3rd Party:  
If you opt to order third-party products or services made available through our site, we may fill in blanks on the order form for your convenience, using account data that you have previously provided us. This data is displayed for your review before the form is submitted, and you will have the option to delete or modify it before the data is sent. When you click to place your order, the data will be sent those 3rd parties. These 3rd parties have agreed to hold this information in confidence, not use it for any purpose except to carry out the service they are providing us, and honor our organization's privacy and security policies in the way this information is handled. WebsiteForever does screen and choose its business partners and affiliates with our privacy goals in mind.

Miscellaneous Information:  
Certain additional non-personal types of information are collected and stored whenever customers interact with us. This information is collected to better develop and offer those products and services which are most desired within our industry. For example, our servers track the page to which customers link from WebsiteForever and the type of Web browser used. No personally identifiable information will be linked to this aggregated information, which may be shared with partners, market researchers and other third parties on an aggregate, non-personally identifiable basis. 

Protection of WebsiteForever and Others:  
Account and other personal information may be released when we are required to do so by law, court order, law enforcement authority or regulatory agency. 

Sites Other Than WebsiteForever:  
We strongly recommend that Customers review the privacy statement and policies of any online service prior to submitting personal information. WebsiteForever has no control over and is not responsible for the gathering practices of other Web sites, including those to which we may link and those which may link to us. 

Enforcement:  
To better protect customer privacy we closely monitor our privacy practices and privacy statements through in-house automated and manual procedures.

Conditions of Use, Concerns:  
By choosing to visit and interact with WebsiteForever web sites, customers agree that their visit and any dispute regarding the protection of their privacy during such visit is subject to this Privacy Statement including, but not limited to, the provisions regarding limitations on damages and the application of the law of the city of Chennai, in Tamil Nadu, India. Please note that if customers enter into other contractual agreements with WebsiteForever, privacy terms and conditions of such other agreements may supplement or supersede this policy. Questions and concerns about privacy at WebsiteForever should be directed to [info@WebsiteForever.com](mailto:info@websiteforever.com).

Revisions or Changes:  
Regardless of later updates or changes to our privacy notice, we will never use the information you submit under our current privacy notice in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.

How to Contact Us:  
Should questions concerning this privacy policy arise, please send us an email at [info@WebsiteForever.com](mailto:info@websiteforever.com). Please specify "Privacy Statement" in the subject line of the e-mail.

WebsiteForever.com   
Effective Date January 20, 2009
